garuda-indonesia.com 2010-12-31

# Privacy Policy Statement - Garuda Indonesia

At **Garuda Indonesia** we recognize that privacy is important. This Privacy Policy applies to all the products, services and information offered by **Garuda Indonesia** on its website. However, there are times we need certain information from you to enable us to serve you better.

 **Garuda Indonesia** is the sole owner of all the information gathered on this website. As a matter of policy we do not share, sell, or rent any information to other parties.

 **Information Browsing**

When you visit our website, we may gather information in the form of "cookie" on your computer, to enable us to recognize when you revisit our web site in the future. Cookies are an extremely small electronic tag which is transferred by a website to the visitor's web browser. Any information gathered from the use of cookies is collated anonymously. Cookies do not gather personal information like name or email address. Cookies measure the effectiveness of our online presence so, we can improve the service we offer. Should you decide not to receive any cookies, or wish to be informed when the cookies are placed, you can configure your web browser accordingly.

 **Security**

 **Garuda Indonesia** understands the need for complete confidentiality of personal information. We endeavor to thoroughly protect your personal information against any loss, manipulation, forgery or unauthorized access for irresponsible purposes.

 **External Links**

Our web Site is designed to enable the links to other websites. **Garuda Indonesia** is not responsible for the privacy policies or lack thereof of other websites. We advise consumers to read carefully the privacy statements of other web sites.

 **Changes of Statement**

 **Garuda Indonesia** reserves the right to change its privacy policy without notice. We recommend visitors to periodically re-read the privacy statement to take note of any changes.
